Yeah.
RINRIN (20)
HOSTESS
It's tough. Mmm.
Hmm?
TAI-CHAN (22)
HAIRSTYLIST
It's okay.
Rinrin, do you want to go back
to the girls' room? All right. Let's go.
Thanks so much for talking to me.
- He's so kind.
- That's friendship.
- All right. Okay.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
KAMAKEN (30)
MMA FIGHTER/BUSINESS OWNER
Rinrin, let's talk.
I'll wait in the classroom.
I'm sorry about everything.
You know,
the fact is, up until now,
you're the one that I've been spending
all my time hanging out with.
And I do like you a lot.
Honestly, it caught me off guard
to hear Mimi say that.
But, you know,
I thought this through.
And I…
want to be with you.
I don't know how to put it,
but from my perspective,
I wish you'd thought about this more.
- I did. That's why we're talking now.
- That's not what I meant.
And besides, I…
never said my feelings wavered.
I was just surprised.
And I didn't want to hide it from you.
No, you said that you like her.
If we're going to be together,
after we leave here…
How do I put this? Like…
Let's say you're back home
and out having drinks
and talking to a girl there.
If she tells you she likes you,
your feelings might waver again.
And that's what made me unsure about us.
Come on. Why would you think that?
I've had so much fun
spending time with you.
There are things
that I've only shared with you.
You're special to me.
And so…
I want you to know,
it's not what you think.
Like, she did tell me to talk to her more,
but I wouldn't go out of my way
to, like, invite Mimi
to come chat with me or anything.
- Okay.
- Right.
So, you know,
I don't want you to get the wrong idea.
Please don't say you'll drop out.
It looks like Rinrin
just can't forgive him anymore, right?
- I want her to forgive him.
- Mmm.
NAGANO
Well, if it isn't Kamaken.
- Hey there.
- Hi there.
I didn't know there was a bench.
- It's always been here.
- Hmm?
- It's been here.
- There we go.
- I'm sitting next to you, if that's okay.
- Go ahead.
Oh, nice.
At first, I didn't think
you were interested in me.
- I convinced myself you weren't.
- Mmm.
- You're impossible to read.
- No, I'm not.
- You are.
- But you know, in relationships,
I'm usually not the one to make
the first move or approach someone.
- I guessed that much.
- I tend to go for a safer option.
- To be honest, I think it comes down to…
- Right.
…some trauma from being cheated on
in a past relationship.
- Wait, that happened?
- Yeah.
If it weren't for him cheating on me,
I probably wouldn't have become a hostess.
- Wow.
- I was so mad at men.
- Like, "Screw them!" You know?
- Yeah. Right.
Like, "I'll just take
all the money I can from men!"
That's one reason I became a hostess.
Also for the money, because working
as a nursery school teacher
didn't pay enough.
Right, right.
So, I was like, "Oh, okay then,"
and started the hostess job.
And since then, I don't go for a man
who doesn't show interest in me first.
I don't make any sort of move
until they make a move.
- Yeah, makes sense.
- So that's just a part of how I operate.
So it's hard for me
to initiate romantic connection.
But, you know, I mean…
How should I say it?
When I heard
that you were interested in me,
I regretted not making a move.
- Mmm-hmm.
- If I'm being honest.
- Yeah.
- But…
I don't think it's right
to suddenly change my mind now.
Yeah.
So, yeah, I wanted to make sure
I shared that with you.
That's why I asked to chat now.
Seriously.
- It's tough being an old lady.
- It's tough being an old man.
- Good luck. Yeah.
- Okay, thanks.
- Say hi to Rinrin.
- Let me know if you need anything.
- Yeah. Thank you.
- Yeah, bye.
- Bye-bye.
- Well done, Kamaken.
- I admire that.
- Good job.
That was just
so incredibly thoughtful of him.
Yeah.
- There we go.
- What's up? It's the last day.
- It's crazy, right?
- Yeah, it went by so fast.
SARA (26)
NAIL ARTIST
KAZUMA (26)
PART-TIMER
Oh, also, I finished the drawing.
Can I see it?
You said you like
sharp and vivid coloring,
so this is what I pictured.
Whoa.
Insane.
I had the feeling
that you might like these colors too.
- Yeah, I like them a lot.
- I thought so.
It's super good. Yeah, that's crazy.
I can't believe you did this so quickly.
Amazing.
I was thinking of you the whole time,
so it was easy to keep going.
Thank you so much. It's insane.
It's just incredible.
I want to keep growing as an artist,
so I'd like to draw something
for you again.
And I could ink you
if I ever become a real tattoo artist.
Definitely. I'd like that.
- I'm looking forward to it. Wow.
- Me too.
But, you know, for me to be successful,
or even get better,
I think with you by my side,
I'd be able to work even harder.
Yeah, I guess so.
If I was there, I could cheer you on.
That's true. Of course.
Also, I feel like
I would make you my priority,
more than anyone else could.
- Mmm.
- And of all the guys here,
I'm the one who likes you the most,
and I believe I can make you the happiest.
That's why I've always been sincere,
and, you know, I've been gravitating
to you this whole time.
I'll put those feelings
into words tomorrow
and share them.
I'll also think deeply about it all.
And share my feelings with you.
Okay.
- Where's the middle?
- There.
- Here?
- Yeah.
- Whoa.
- Hey.
- Still talking? It's taking forever.
- No.
RYOPI (29)
BAR OWNER
- Of course. It's the last day.
- He's gonna write "Graduation."
- Wanna write it?
- Okay, sure.
Be right back. Gotta pee.
Just let me write this one.
- There!
- Nice.
- How does it look?
- Looks good.
GRADUATION
- I told Sara how I feel, so no regrets.
- Yeah?
- I bet.
- Tomorrow's the day.
- The showdown?
- Yeah, the showdown.
Do your best.
- And you do the same.
- You're like, "Are you patronizing me?"
- You do your best too.
- Like, "How dare you interrupt us?"
You're damn right.
You surprised me, coming in like that.
I thought you were full of crap at first.
I mean, I also have my reasons, of course.
- We'll be proper men, right?
- Sure.
- You think you'll win?
- Piece of cake.
- Against the great me?
- No problem.
That's the spirit.
Otherwise, it's not worth the effort.
Of course. I'm a real man.
Oh, these two have a good relationship.
Yeah, their friendship is nice, right?
- Okay.
- See ya.
Tomorrow, we're enemies.
Shut up. Just leave already, punk.
I'll knock you out. For real!
I have no regrets at this point.
Because I was determined.
I only had eyes for Sara
for the past two weeks.
- I think you're the one I click most with.
- Oh. Why's that?
You know,
in terms of how effortless it is.
Yeah, in the end, I don't know, it's like,
when I take everything
into account, it's you.
It has to be you.
Oh.
- Stop saying "Oh."
- No, I'm glad.
I am, I swear.
- It's nothing.
- Okay.
So, I'm thinking, like, I had a girlfriend
for about five years, you know?
- Right, you told me.
- Right, yeah.
- And being with her was too much trouble.
- Hmm.
But that relationship
was a serious one for me.
Mmm.
And now, I don't know
how to be in love like that anymore.
Right. Same here.
But then,
I guess it's okay if I don't know.
Like, if you fall in love too hard,
that can be trouble, right?
Yeah, you're right.
That's why I think it's okay
to keep a comfortable distance.
And you're the person
who keeps the best distance from me.
- Is that a compliment?
- It's a compliment.
This is a compliment, for sure.
Isn't it nice? Hassle-free is great.
- A comfortable distance?
- Yeah.
Well, I guess that's true.
- Right.
That's why, taking all that into account,
I think you're the one for me.
You've got a point.
It's pretty amazing.
I think this resonated with me the most.
- Really?
- You're always making jokes.
Right?
- But I thought I'd be serious today.
- That's because it's the last day!
- Yeah.
- It'd be bad if you didn't.
Right.
Let's see, how do I put it?
It's almost like
you're sharing your mind with someone?
The good and the bad.
And I realized that it's important
to communicate the good stuff
and the annoying stuff.
Yeah, and I was reminded once again
how I should cherish the moment
and focus on the present.
Even if she chooses Kazuma,
I won't have any regrets. None.
Yeah. Even if she picks Kazuma
or someone else, I'll be content.
I think I communicated that,
so I think I'm good.
Hmm. I'm having trouble choosing.
I'm not sure yet.
Kazuma tells me
how he feels about me pretty directly.
But I've never heard Ryopi
share those feelings.
"I'm interested in you."
Or like, "Out of everyone here,
I'd choose you."
And that kind of makes me feel
like I'm just a leftover.
So there's a part of me that wonders
if he's being real.
So I want to hear how he truly feels
when he confesses.
If he's just still making jokes,
I might not choose him.
When they confess their feelings,
if either of them says the right things
and convinces me
that they're the right guy for me,
then I might just trust my feelings
and choose in that moment.
But if I still can't shake
this feeling of uncertainty,
I might have to say no to both of them.
Yeah.
- So, she had some concerns.
- That came as a surprise, right?
- I thought she was set on Ryopi.
- Me too.
Yeah. They said they were
on the same wavelength.
But, come to think of it,
Ryopi hasn't said anything like,
"I have strong feelings for you,
and I'll be devoted to you."
I was surprised that Sara actually wanted
to hear that from him.
- You're right, I totally agree.
- She wanted him to make it clear.
- Yeah.
- Right?
- That took me by surprise, honestly.
Hey, you forgot your bag.
- Oh, thank you.
- Here.
I thought I'd left it,
but I was going to go get it later.
- You're very kind.
- No worries.
KAHOCHI (20)
HOSTESS
- It's the last day.
- The last day.
So, you know, yesterday,
I was gonna ask you for a one-on-one
if I didn't have a fever.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, but then you came
to the girls' room.
So, at that point,
I was glad I had a fever.
- For real?
- Yeah.
- So we could talk?
- Yeah. I was like, "Lucky me."
So, you were a transfer student,
- and you were only here for a week.
- Yeah.
But I wish I'd talked to you more
- while we had the time.
- Mmm.
Yeah, I felt the same way.
And that's why I feel like
if I had three more days,
I wouldn't have any regrets.
- So, you still have some regrets?
- Of course I do.
Because I decided to focus on you
just yesterday, or the day before.
- Seriously?
- Really.
Yeah, so…
You've liked Sara from day one, right?
I thought you were a very devoted
and sincere person.
And that kind of made me
like you even more.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah, yeah.
- That's nice to hear, you know.
- Yeah?
I've never had a girl
catch feelings for me first.
Right, right.
- I've never been popular with girls.
- I see.
So, like… How should I put it?
- When it's telling someone how I feel…
- Yeah.
…it's easy, because I just have
to be honest with myself.
But, like, flirting and stuff,
getting someone to fall for me
- is not my thing.
- I see.
- Because I'm not very good with words.
- Makes sense.
- Yeah.
- But that's nice, you know?
- That awkward side of you. You know…
- You think so?
You're genuine and sincere,
and that's what I liked about you.
You're great the way you are.
- You know that…
- Yeah?
- …I have a kid?
- Sure.
- So, I think that you're amazing.
- Mmm.
Because right now, my ex-wife
is in the same situation as you.
- And that is a tough spot to be in.
- Mmm-hmm.
Of course, it's only natural as a man
for me to support financially,
but that alone doesn't make me a good dad.
Right, yeah.
The only thing I can say to her is,
"I'm sorry for not being able
to be together with you."
That's why I'm really,
you know, super grateful
to my ex-wife for all she does.
Mmm-hmm.
- You're only 20, but still.
- Mmm.
I think it's so cool
that you're living your life
as a grown woman.
- Yeah.
- I do.
Hello there.
Hi, Mom, how is it going?
- Wow.
- What are you doing?
I was drinking milk.
- You were drinking milk?
- Yeah.
You know,
Mommy has been learning a lot here.
- Yeah.
- You know what it means?
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah, so that means,
once I come home,
Mommy's going to try extra hard.
I'll wipe your tears.
You'll wipe my tears? Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Remember, it's gonna be okay.
It will, because I love you.
Because you love me? Thank you.
I love you too.
Thank you so much
- for always wiping my tears.
- Yeah.
You're the best.
It's okay.
- You know, your mommy…
- Yeah?
…will do her best tomorrow,
and then she'll come home, okay?
Okay. You can do it, Mommy.
I can, right?
I love you, Mommy.
You love me?
Thank you.
Bye-bye!
Well, even if he likes Sara more,
I want him to know
that I had a big crush on him
so that he can reflect on it later.
So, tomorrow at graduation, I'm going
to be completely honest with Kazuma
and tell him how I feel about him.
I know that I want to honor
my own feelings, but also,
I want to be sure I honor the feelings
of someone who cares about me.
Even though Kahochi told me
that she just started
having these feelings for me,
they're still feelings
that I want to fully accept in my heart.
I'm not…
a super smart guy,
and there's still this person
who wants to be with me.
So her feelings are something
I definitely want to acknowledge.
I want to make sure
I take her feelings seriously.
You know, if Kahochi
hadn't shared these feelings with him,
Kazuma wouldn't be wavering.
- He's not that kind of a guy.
- Mmm.
But if someone says something like that,
and you've never heard it before,
you're going to question things,
no matter how strong your feelings are.
- Right?
- I see.
So? How do you feel?
Be honest.
RUNE (28)
RAPPER/BUSINESS OWNER
- I imagine you're probably torn.
- Yeah.
Mmm, if I'm being honest…
there was a time when I thought
that I should stop thinking about you…
for a while.
But to me,
that felt like I was running away.
And a part of me was wondering
if it was okay to give up so quickly.
Truthfully, if you hadn't
joined our group…
I'm not sure I would have
ever fallen in love at all in this school.
- I feel the same way.
- Mmm.
- Mimi, I have strong feelings for you.
- Hmm.
I want to honor you and cherish you.
And I want to work hard for you
because of that.
Those feelings
are unlikely to change.
Whenever I'm in trouble,
you're always the one who helps me.
Mmm.
- Hmm. You know?
- Hmm.
Well, I've given her everything I've got,
and I left absolutely nothing
on the table.
I just gotta stay committed and be honest,
as I focus on Mimi.
I'll give it my all.
I hope I can make her smile,
and we both go home together.
I think up till now,
I've been a bit of a coward,
and I wasn't good at trusting people.
But they're so…
How should I put it?
I mean, I don't think
I've ever had the chance
to meet people who would pursue me
so directly and passionately.
And to be completely honest,
I still can't make up my mind
at this point.
Well, either I choose one of them,
or I don't choose any of them.
Hmm. I think it will have to be
one of those two choices.
Yeah. I mean, I still can't quite tell
if she even wants to choose
any of these three guys,
- even though graduation is tomorrow.
- Yeah, yeah.
This victim mentality
that she's held on to
is something she needs to step out of.
- Otherwise, nothing will change.
- Yeah.
- And isn't this a great opportunity?
- Right?
- To change at this school?
- Yeah.
Yeah, so, choosing someone…
- …is a must.
I hope she chooses someone.
MARU (28)
HOST/PRESIDENT
I've already decided on the girl
I want to confess to. Mmm.
That said, there's this girl
who has feelings for me,
and now I know
the depth of those feelings.
Mmm.
I don't know how I'll react
when I hear her confess.
Like, it's hard to predict
how I'm going to feel when that happens.
I'm being totally real with you.
Yeah.
Tomorrow, I want to confess to Maru.
AYACHERU (24)
HOSTESS
Yeah. Well, I don't mind
if he rejects me, actually.
I mean, I think my chances are probably…
close to zero.
But, okay, I'll just do
what I have to do, you know?
Maru was the one
I spent the most time with.
Like, we were together
from the beginning until the end.
So, when I think about it,
there's a part of me who wants
to tell him how grateful I am.
Yeah.
Hey.
- I wanted to see you.
- Okay.
SHARAN (21)
LOUNGE HOSTESS
So, like I said yesterday,
I've always liked you.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Yeah.
Your feelings are…
- I think you heard them loud and clear.
- 1,000%, yeah.
- Yeah.
- They're crystal clear, for sure.
Right.
But there are times
when I feel like I don't know anymore.
Mmm.
I mean, you never know,
they might change again tonight.
- I mean…
- Yeah.
You know what?
You and I actually have
something in common.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Mmm.
When we wanted to run away,
we faced it instead.
- Yeah, that's true. I did try to run away.
- Right? But you faced it.
- We're similar, aren't we?
- Mmm-hmm. Yeah.
We are. I also wanted to run away. But…
I feel like both of us
changed at this school. For sure.
- A lot.
- So much.
I can face things now.
- Yeah.
- I gained that strength while I was here.
- Hmm.
- For sure.
- I'll always remember this.
- Me too.
- Forever.
Seriously. I'm super happy.
Yeah.
Tomorrow, we might have
to say goodbye to everyone.
No, no, I don't want to do that yet. Mmm.
I'm not ready for that.
- I know.
- I really don't want to.
I like you so much, it hurts.
Seriously, so much.
Oh no, I kissed you.
Jeez.
Lift me up?
Sure, I can do that.
Oh!
- This might be the last time, so…
- Yeah.
…I can be clingy.
- I like you so much, Tai-chan.
- Mmm. Yeah.
I feel blessed.
Like, hmm…
There might be a chance,
so I have to believe in it and in myself.
- Wow!
- She really changed.
When I talked to Sharan one last time,
my heart wavered for a moment.
I mean, I wonder why.
You know, this quote crossed my mind
in that moment.
Something like,
"Love the woman that loves you."
Yeah.
- Whose quote is that?
- Who said that?
"Love the woman that loves you."
- What? Who was he quoting?
- Come on, who said that?
Where did he hear something like that?
- What a selfish quote.
- Absolutely.
Tonight is the last night.
Everyone, please gather
in the schoolyard now.
- What is this?
- Wait, what are we looking at?
- What is this, seriously?
- Is it a magic show?
It's the prime time of their life.
There's still one day left,
but up till now, we've given our all.
We all worked together
to get to this moment.
And I'm proud of that.
Thank you for coming into my life.
I came here to find love,
but I ended up learning a lot of things,
not just about romance.
We've all changed for the better
over the past two weeks.
I realized that it's okay to be myself.
Spending time with you all
has taught me so much, for real.
I don't know, like, seriously,
these have probably been
the most intense two weeks
of my entire life so far,
and I'm sure they always will be.
Are those manly tears?
Hello?
- Oh, hello?
- Hi.
- Is this Bo?
- Yeah. Been a while.
Yeah, it has. How are you?
I'm doing good. What's up?
- Yeah, so, like, Part 1 ended.
- Right.
And then one of the Part 2 members
gave me a baptism of fire.
You show 'em what you got?
Oh, you know, maybe just a little.
Anyone there as good as me?
No way, no one can top you.
You're right.
And, you know,
somehow, I feel like
I've been a lot more myself in Part 2.
But then…
Yeah?
Mmm, the ones that made me feel that way
are the people I'd already met in Part 1.
So, I'm super grateful for that.
If you feel that way,
that means you have grown a bit more.
Yeah.
Me too, you know.
I made some changes when I was there.
Yeah. So, like…
this time I'll be sure
to make it a success.
And I'm thinking I'll… bring home
a cute girlfriend,
so I want you to root for me.
- Isn't that adorable?
- Yeah.
Just do what you think is right,
whatever the result may be.
- Don't be someone that you're not.
- Yeah, you're right.
- I'll do it my way. I'll stay true…
- Yeah.
- …to myself.
- Okay. Do your best.
Mmm, thank you.
Well, I'll be cheering for you.
Yeah. I appreciate it.
Next time I see you,
I'll be a more mature version of myself.
That goes for both of us.
- I'll be more mature too.
- Okay.
- Thanks, Tai-chan.
- Same to you.
- Thanks for calling and talking with me.
- Of course. Yeah, see you.
- Yeah.
- Okay, bye-bye.
- Okay, good night.
- Night.
He's just adorable--
I'll do my best.
- That was Bo Sensei making an appearance…
- Bo!
- Bo was so nice.
- …after a long hiatus.
"He's adorable." Beep, beep.
I thought he died or something.
He hung up
while he was still talking, right?
- Maybe he called because he wanted a push.
- I think you're right. For sure.
- Like, "Okay, I'll do it!"
- He's wavering between two girls.
Sharan and Mimi. He can't decide.
- I want him to choose Sharan.
- And Sharan has changed too.
- Yeah.
- She's like a completely different person.
- Exactly.
- She's really changed.
She told him straight up
that she liked him.
- And as for Rinrin and Kamaken…
- Mmm.
…we actually don't know
- if she's gonna say yes to his confession.
- Right, we don't.
Because Rinrin seems like,
once her mind is set, her mind is set.
- Yeah.
- She has that tendency, and it shows.
So, unless Kamaken decides
to say something
- or do something impactful…
- Right.
…I don't think
he can change Rinrin's mind.
But they're all very straightforward
with their feelings
- during the confession.
- Yeah. Right.
And sometimes, that's when
they finally make up their minds.
The words that they choose
to say at the very end
make a huge difference too.
BADLY IN LOVE
GRADUATION
CONGRATULATIONS!
BADLY IN LOVE
TAI-CHAN
KAZUMA
RYOPI
RUNE
MARU
KAMAKEN
SHARAN
MIMI
SARA
RINRIN
AYACHERU
KAHOCHI
GRADUATION
We will now begin the graduation ceremony.
When you hear your name called,
please step forward,
call out the person you have feelings for,
and confess your true feelings to them.
- I'm nervous.
- First up, Sharan.
Yes.
First of all, I'd like to thank you all
for the past two weeks.
Doing things in a group setting
has never felt comfortable to me,
to be honest.
But then,
I didn't expect to…
I didn't think I could get along
with anyone at first,
but then I did.
And in the end, I think I learned a lot.
And as far as romance goes, you know,
I didn't think
I could find it here at all.
I think, emotionally, I felt so unstable.
But now, I feel I'm much stronger,
thanks to all of you.
So, I'm glad I met you all.
This is something I'll never, ever forget.
So, at this graduation ceremony,
I want to convey my love
without holding anything back.
So…
Tai-chan.
Yes.
From the first day,
you were the one
I ended up talking to the most.
And gradually, I started to like you.
But then, I have these flaws,
you might call them.
Like, because I liked you so much,
it made me jealous.
And I would cry all the time.
But I decided I'm not giving up.
This is my last chance.
This is the first time in my entire life
that I am the one who confesses.
So…
please go out with me.
- First of all…
- Yeah.
…thank you for sharing
your feelings with me.
Yeah.
- I was also interested in you.
- Mmm.
- And you and I went through a lot.
- We did.
Like, you got mad at me and cried. Yeah.
I always hoped that you would change.
- I also need to change myself…
- Right.
…in many ways.
And, at some point,
your expression started to brighten,
and it seemed like you changed a lot.
I definitely noticed.
But, you know, mmm…
- I still think…
- Yeah?
- …there's someone I can't give up on.
- Ah.
- So in the end…
- Sure.
…I want to give my all
and share my love with her.
- That's what I feel. Mmm.
- Okay.
- But thank you for coming into my life.
- Likewise.
- I'm sorry.
- No, it's okay.
- Totally fine. I should thank you.
- Oh?
- I got to open my heart to you.
- Ah.
And I'm not crying.
- Wow, look at Sharan's face.
- So nice.
- Wonderful.
- Sharan was great.
Well done, Sharan.
She's grown so much.
She didn't cry at all.
Next up is…
Kamaken.
Yes.
First of all,
I joined much later.
So I was worried
about whether I could fall in love.
But then,
I felt more youthful and passionate here
than I did when I was actually in school,
in my younger days.
To me, this truly was
an invaluable experience in my life.
I got to interact with a lot of people
and saw different approaches to life
and learned what being cool
actually means, as a man.
I did everything I could.
And during it all,
while I was here at this school,
I fell in love with a girl.
Rinrin.
Yes.
- Oh?
- Oh, she smiled!
Look at that!
Rinrin.
You were the first person
to ask me out on a date after I got here.
That date was so much fun.
I was so attracted to you.
On the outside, you're so gyaru.
It's intimidating.
That's how I felt at first.
But watching how you face things head-on…
made me fall for you so quickly.
I still have a lot to work on
so I can mature.
Mmm.
But you made me realize
that age doesn't matter.
And with you,
I want to…
keep growing as a person by your side.
So, please, go out with me.
First of all, was it one week?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
Um, how do I put this?
Since I lived in Miyagi Prefecture when
the Great East Japan Earthquake happened…
Yeah?
- …I knew some of the people that died.
- Right.
Since then,
I've had trouble with my friends,
and I got into fist fights
and stuff like that.
I've dealt with a lot of pain.
But after what I've been through,
I came here and met you.
How do I say this?
I couldn't be myself before,
but now I feel like I can.
This was the first time I felt that way.
I kept watching you
and saw how you always…
try your best at everything,
and I found myself attracted to you.
And before I knew it, I had a crush.
So, yes, I'd be happy to go out with you.
- I look forward to it.
- Likewise.
Oh, they did it!
- Yeah!
- Oh my gosh, so great!
- They look great.
- Whoa!
I got lipstick on you.
Yay!
Congrats, Kamaken!
- Congrats!
- Thank you!
- We were worried, weren't we?
- So happy for them.
Definitely.
So manly.
- Thank you.
- I was so nervous.
Next up is…
Kahochi.
Yes.
I mean, like…
Mmm, I made a friend
that I can now call my bestie.
And I also have some big sisters here
that I can talk to forever.
And all the boys are kind.
Mmm, at the very end of this,
I found someone that I like.
So today,
I want to properly tell him how I feel.
And that man is Kazuma, of course.
Yes.
Hmm. I'm so nervous that I don't know
if I can convey it to you properly.
When we talked
about how both of us are parents,
I thought that you must be someone
who is considerate to kids.
That's when I started
to be interested in you.
And the fact
that you have always liked Sara
from the beginning,
without being distracted by others,
made me see you as a strong man.
I think it's wonderful
to be devoted to one person.
When I was sick and I had a fever,
you brought me some jelly.
That made me so happy.
And then, as I was watching you leave,
I realized in that moment, you were kind,
and I was glad it was you.
I didn't want it to be anyone else.
I have feelings for you, Kazuma.
So, first of all, thank you so much.
This has never happened to me before.
I've never been pursued by a girl
in my entire life.
When it comes to romance,
I'm always the one doing the chasing.
Now, for the first time, you're telling me
that you have feelings for me first,
and it felt good to hear that.
It made me think that I…
should definitely not
treat your feelings lightly.
I shouldn't dismiss them.
So I'm taking them very seriously.
But the truth is, there's been someone
I've been interested in
since the first day.
Today's the graduation ceremony,
and I plan to be honest with her
about my feelings.
But thank you so much
for opening up to me.
- Yeah.
- I'll never forget what you shared.
- Mmm.
- Thank you.
I wish you the best of luck.
Mmm.
- Seriously?
- Come on!
- For real?
- Seriously?
A valiant effort, Kahochi.
Next up is…
Ayacheru.
Oh no. Okay.
Oh jeez.
Okay, so,
I mean, first of all, I just want to say,
after spending two weeks
back in school, I just…
How should I put it?
There were so many things
I learned through this experience.
And I think it's because
we all have similar pasts,
and that's why we were able
to empathize with each other.
So, I guess I want to say first
that I'm glad to have met all of you.
And as we got to know each other,
there's someone…
who was always there for me,
from the beginning to the end,
and I'd like to tell him how I feel.
So, Maru…
- Yes.
- Please come here.
I'm so nervous.
This is so scary.
Okay, so…
Well, from the very start, until the end,
you know, somehow, I think that, for me…
How do I say it?
Well, at first, you were the one
who would talk to me the most.
And after a while,
I started thinking to myself
that this whole time,
you're the one I'd always end up
gravitating to, honestly.
Even though, you know,
I still wanted to talk to other guys too.
But then, in the end,
somewhere deep down in my heart,
I always felt like I just wanted
to go and talk to you.
And part of me wondered,
"What does it actually mean
to like someone?"
So, I guess I just wasn't sure
what those feelings meant for me.
But as the days went by,
and as I kept talking to you
and getting to know you,
I noticed I felt comfortable around you.
I felt like I could relax
and just be myself
whenever I was spending time with you.
When I was with you,
I felt the most comfortable
being my true self.
And that made me realize
that I had romantic feelings for you.
That's how I came to have
a crush on you, Maru.
Thank you for that.
She said, "Thank you."
It's amazing that she thanked him
for making her fall for him.
Mmm.
Well, I'm grateful that
you were always straightforward with me
about your feelings for me.
You talked to me a lot
and spent a lot of time with me.
I enjoyed that, yeah.
At first, I didn't quite know
what to make
of the feelings I had for you.
Mmm.
I'd lost my sense of what romance was,
so I came here to find it
and was confused at first.
But it's not like I spent time with you
just because you approached me.
I was also taking it seriously. Yeah.
I talked to you
because there were things about you
that made me want
to spend more time with you.
For sure.
And then, during the time
when I was unable to give it my all, um…
I met someone that I was interested in.
I started wanting to know more about her.
So, given that there's a woman
I want to pour my heart out to today,
I can't return your feelings,
but I wish you the best.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
- Maru.
- She was brave.
- Ayacheru did well. Right?
- Come on, man.
She shared her feelings,
knowing he probably felt differently.
- Yeah, that's what's so hard.
- You're right about that.
- Ah, man.
- Mmm.
I know, right?
This is so tough.
Next up is…
Kazuma.
Yes.
You know, I came to truly love
every one of you, as individuals.
So, I'm so happy that we're able
to graduate together like this.
Sara, Sharan, Mimi, Ayacheru.
Sharan, Rinrin.
Wait, hold on.
Just start over.
Oh, man, I'm a little nervous.
Stop it, seriously. You're hilarious.
You got this.
Yeah.
I feel like you all helped me graduate.
Thank you, everyone.
For the past two weeks,
I've had feelings for someone,
and I'm going to tell her how I feel.
Sara.
Yes.
Hold on a second.
- So, on the first day…
- Yeah?
From the moment
you walked into the classroom,
I was attracted to you.
I just had a gut feeling about you.
From that moment,
I wanted to get to know you better.
While we were all doing our best
to live together,
I saw you take the initiative
to cook for everyone here.
Mmm.
And sometimes,
you would show your vulnerable side.
The way you care deeply
about your friends…
and the way you express
your strong sense of self,
those are things I respect so much.
I got to know you a little bit
over the past two weeks,
but I want to get to know
so much more about you.
I could know you even better
if you would stay by my side.
Over the past two weeks,
there's been no doubt
that my feelings for you
have never wavered in the slightest.
Please be with me.
Um, so, there was a point at which…
- I didn't have anyone I was interested in.
- Mmm.
So, while everyone
was going on one-on-one dates,
I was sitting alone in the living room.
I had lots of moments like that,
but then you reached out to me.
You invited me to talk for the first time.
- Mmm.
- Yeah.
And so, as we kept talking,
while still keeping
a comfortable distance,
I came to realize
we were actually similar in many ways.
And from that point on,
I gradually became interested in you.
So I called you out
in the PA announcement event.
And before I knew it,
I developed serious feelings for you.
So, I know we've only been talking
about silly stuff together,
but I hope we can keep talking
about silly stuff
and have even more fun together
and become romantic partners.
- Yeah.
- That's what I hope.
I have feelings for you.
Please be with me.
He was finally direct about his feelings.
He nailed it.
Wow, I have no idea who she'll pick.
First, Kazuma…
From the first day,
you kept telling me
that you were only interested in me.
Thank you.
These two weeks were hard for me at times,
but you were always there for me.
You always told me
exactly how you felt
about me.
What I mean is,
I thought you were incredible.
You also told me
you wanted to draw something for me,
and you gave it to me.
That was very moving for me.
But…
Mmm.
My heart doesn't feel
romantic love for you.
Instead, to me, you feel more like
an irreplaceable friend.
And so, you're someone I want to root for
with all of my heart.
Please keep striving
for what you want in this life,
but I can't be by your side.
I'm sorry.
And, Ryopi…
Yes.
We talked and laughed a lot
and got excited
talking about crude things,
almost nonstop, it felt like.
At first,
I wasn't all that interested in you,
but we started having
one-on-ones every day.
Honestly, I couldn't tell
if your feelings were real.
But now, you were just…
straightforward
about your feelings for me.
And, you know, people can worry
about the future forever,
and no one knows what will happen.
So I'm standing here now,
ready to trust my gut and make a decision.
And right now, my gut is telling me
that I think it would be nice
to spend more time with you, Ryopi.
I look forward to being with you.
Likewise.
- So it was Ryopi in the end.
- Yeah, looks like it was Ryopi.
Thank you.
Aw, Kazuma. Of course.
He was so devoted to her.
Keep it together.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Kazuma, thank you.
- Please make Sara happy.
- Of course.
Rivals in love.
But these two also had a friendship.
They went head-to-head with respect.
Yeah.
Next up is…
Rune.
All right.
- Mmm, this is the main event.
- It sure is.
To all of you, including those
who have already left the gym,
I love every one of you.
I went to the sauna.
I went on dates.
And when I was away for a little while…
and I came back to school,
you all welcomed me back with open arms.
Those moments made me so happy.
I think coming to this school
and meeting everyone
made me grow as a person.
I'm grateful to all of you.
Thank you.
During all of that,
I found…
…someone I really like.
Mimi, please join me.
- So, what is she going to do?
- Make up your mind.
- It comes down to her decision.
- Right.
Rune.
I must interrupt.
I have to interrupt you as well.
Bring it on.
Mimi, first,
thank you for coming into my life.
You made my life at school so great.
When you first walked into the classroom,
I seriously thought
you were just a stubborn girl.
That was my impression.
At that time, I just wasn't interested
or developing feelings for you at all.
But the more I got to know you,
the more I found myself attracted to you.
Before long, I was crazy about you.
The way you care about your family…
I can see how much you cherish them.
I'm the same way.
And I like that kind
and gentle side of you.
When you're angry, you show it.
When you're sad, you cry.
I've seen so many sides of you.
And now, I like you very much.
You always told me
that I'm your hero.
But from now on,
I don't want to just be your hero.
I want to be your man.
I want you to be with me.
I care about you. Please go out with me.
First of all,
for everything so far, I thank you.
I've told you so many times
that I like you.
I wrote "I like Mimi so much"
on the beach,
and it was the truth.
And, well,
as we spent time living together,
my feelings for you
kept growing every day.
Yeah. There are the things
we talked about at the beach,
like our age difference and our futures.
Honestly, I still think
that those things are irrelevant,
and I'm going to prove that
to you, for sure.
Mmm-hmm.
I'm a pretty clumsy person,
so you do laugh at me a lot, but…
despite that, you still made me feel
like I want you by my side forever.
Mmm.
I'll get straight to the point.
I want you to come with me.
I will definitely make you happy.
That's all.
Um, Mimi.
You're probably a very strong woman,
but there must be a side of you
that you don't show others.
That was my first impression of you.
And that was the side of you
I was most curious about.
And the more we talked,
and the more time we spent together,
I noticed something
that I thought was wonderful.
You took each of us seriously
and considered romance with us earnestly.
I thought that with you,
I could have the relationship
that I've been searching for,
and that's how I fell in love.
You gave a great first impression.
On day one, you were strong,
beautiful, and very mature.
But I also know there's a vulnerable side.
I believe I am best suited to listen
and understand that side of you as well.
And I don't mean
just the guys at this school.
Even in the real world,
I will understand you the best,
and I hope for the opportunity
to support you.
Please let me show you that support.
Please go out with me.
What? She's deciding in the moment?
- She's thinking.
- Oh, I'm so nervous!
Go for it, Mimi.
- Overcome your trauma.
- That's right.
I'm sorry, one second.
Can I start with Maru?
With you, Maru,
as we talked, I thought
that you were very understanding
of what I do for a living.
We've talked so much,
and you are always thoughtful about it.
I always thought
that was very sweet of you.
But, you know…
…I don't think I can be
that understanding
of the work that you do.
So…
…I cannot return the feelings
that you have for me.
- Thank you.
- I'm so sorry.
Tai-chan, may I?
Mmm.
Yeah, so, Tai-chan,
when I first met you,
my impression was that you looked unusual
and that you were only 22.
And you had already flunked Part 1.
I was like, "Why is he here?"
I had a very negative impression of you.
Mmm.
I just saw you
as someone who was very young.
And then we started going on one-on-ones,
and the way you express yourself
is much more mature
than a typical 22-year-old.
You were the most… How do I say it?
My heart just naturally fluttered the most
when I was with you.
But, still…
I don't know, I…
I guess I'm just not
the type of person who takes risks.
I know how strongly you feel,
but I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Rune, may I?
Of course.
Hmm, when I… first met you here,
I got the impression from you
that you were a very good listener.
And when
the missing meal incident happened,
you were the first to notice.
If you hadn't suggested
that we eat in the kitchen,
to be completely honest with you,
I don't think
I would be standing here right now.
And from that point on, you know,
I was somehow able
to hang out with the other girls.
And as we continued sharing
this experience and living together,
we had our one-on-ones
and our overnight date,
and I thought that it was very admirable
that you are such a sincere person.
And the thing that made me the happiest
was that you were always
the first to notice
when I was in trouble.
I'm already 29 years old,
but I still have a childish side,
as I'm sure everyone knows.
I'm still…
How do I say it?
I want to support someone,
but I also want to…
be supported.
And so, I…
want to support you, Rune.
And I want you to be the one
who supports me too.
Thank you.
Whoa…
Did that just happen?
I had absolutely no idea.
Me neither,
but I didn't think she would choose Rune.
But, you know,
love isn't just about
how well people flirt.
Thank you.
Tai-chan!
I mean, can he get another confession?
To Sharan?
Tai-chan.
Kazuma, you were so cool.
That concludes our graduation ceremony.
- So it's over!
- Hey, Sharan. Sharan.
Oh, go for it!
- Thank you.
- It's fine, go for it. It's okay.
Maybe it's starting?
- I hope that's true.
- I hope so too.
- It's okay to try, right?
- Yeah, it is! Sure, sure.
It's fine to start something new.
- It's fine.
- Totally.
- You did it.
- Little sister. You did well.
- You too, Kazuma.
- Same to you.
BADLY IN LOVE
GRADUATION
- Oh, I'm starting to feel sad.
- It's bittersweet.
- I know.
- I wonder why.
- Because it's ending?
- Yeah, it's coming to an end.
KAHOCHI
OKINAWA
SARA
SHARAN
SGS MOTORCYCLE CLUB
AYACHERU
RINRIN
FIRST OF ALL,
THANKS RYOPI FOR EVERYTHING
LOVE
KAZUMA
REPRESENTING KABUKICHO!!
TAI-CHAN - NOTORIOUS
SAFETY FIRST - FOREST SAUNA
KAMAKEN
LOVE
You know, they really go for it.
They face each other head-on
and lock horns.
- Right.
- Mmm.
That's what makes them
so wonderful and exciting.
It inspires us too,
to live our lives in earnest.
- Yes. 100%.
- That's how it feels.
- Yeah, truly.
- Mmm.
I miss them already!
- Me too.
- So much.
I miss them too.
Please repeat the year.
Okay.